本:回头见,爸爸,我跟肯尼去看电影去了.
Ben: See you later dad, I'm going to the movies with Kenny.
杰森:本,上次我跟你严肃地谈了,
Jason: Ben what did I tell you to do the last time you and I had
让你干什么去来着?
a serious talk
本:哦,等我结婚以后再说吧.
Ben: Hmm wait till I'm married.
杰森:不!!去扫树叶去.
Jason: No!!Rake the leaves.
本:哦,算了吧,
Ben: Oh come on dad,
爸爸,
Handy man Bob is guaranteed to be the bloodiest horra movie of all time,
现在人人都说是有史以来最棒的一部恐怖片.又不用你付钱.
you don't barff you don't pay.
杰森:你都看过5遍了.
Jason: You have seen it five times.
本:哦,哦,白看不厌啊.
Ben: Ah not without barffing.
杰森:干活去.亲爱的,
Jason: Great.Sweetheart where have you been,
你去哪里了?轮胎大王马里一个小时前就开门了.
mary the tire king opened it's doors an hour ago .
麦琪:我去拿写专栏需要的吸尘器去了.
Maggie: I was picking up a vacuum cleaners to test for my column.
杰森:快点,各位.
Jason: Come on everybody who get to the tire store before noon,
谁在中午之前赶到轮胎店,就能免费得到干果吃.
gets free lug nuts .
也许我们可以粘上假胡子,多去两躺.
Maggie: Maybe we should put on fake mustaches and go back twice .
杰森:快点,本.
Jason: Come on Ben I want you to take these vacuum back for your mother
帮你妈妈把这些吸尘器搬进去,再扫树叶.
and rake the leaves .
本:搬箱子,扫树叶,
Ben: Carry the boxes, rake the leaves, sweep the beach,
整草坪,也许你还想把房子向左再移一下呢.
maybe you would like the house moved a little bit to the left too.
肯尼:嘿,本,
Kenny: Hey Ben let's jam,
你到是快点啊.我们不能错过"灵巧人鲍伯"把那个老太太绑到轮椅上的那场戏.
we don't want to miss handy man bob hot grooving that old lady to her rocker .
本:不能去了.我爸爸让我扫这些该死的树叶呢.
Ben: I can't my dads making me rake these stupid leaves.
肯尼:嘿,用一下这个.
Kenny: So use one of those,
把吸尘器的管子倒装一下就是吹风机了.
move the holes from the intake to the exhaust and it's a blower.
本:我不能碰妈妈的吸尘器.那是用来写专栏的.
Ben: I can't touch my moms' vacuums, they're for a column.
肯尼:那可遭了,我们肯定会错过"灵巧人鲍伯"把那些坏蛋的鼻子打歪了的那场戏了.
Kenny: To bad cause you're going to miss the part where handy man bob blow
the interlation up that guys nose
本:哦,天啊.我喜欢那场戏,但去不了.
Ben: Oh God I love that seen, but no .
肯尼:好吧.我去给你占个座位,万一你能来的话.
Kenny: OK.But I'll save you a sit in case you get smart .
本:把它当吹风机用,我可以试试.这恐怕不好.
Ben: Use it as a blower, I could do that, it would be wrong.
为本报仇,使劲地吹吧.快滚吧,
Blow hart two Ben's revenge, take that you crunchy little leaves,
小树叶们.哈哈,看它们狼狈的样子.
ha ha ha look at them run.
呃,哈,叶子皇后们害怕了,尝尝滋味吧,陛下.你们可以滚,但不能藏起来.噢.
Uh huh the queens fear rode, want a taste of this your majesty.You can
roll queeny but you can not hide.Oops
本:好吧,别慌张,
Ben: Ok let's not panic, maybe it wouldn't be so bad,
也许还没那么遭呢.也许妈妈会理解的.
maybe mom will understand.
麦琪:你这不是在毁我的事业嘛,你想胡闹到20岁吗?
Maggie: This is my career you're messing with, your grounded till your 20.
本:我还是告诉爸爸吧,他的脾气好多了.
Ben: Maybe I better tell dad, he's not so emotional.
杰森:本,我要掐断你的脖子.
Jason: Ben I'm going to break your neck .
本:你们快点啊,他们眼看就要回来了.
Ben: Would you hurry it up, my folks will be home anytime second.
肯尼:别急三火四的,细致的工作需要时间.
Kenny: Don't be bugging, precision work takes time.
本:你还在抱怨我没让你去看电影.
Ben: You still mad at me for jaragging you out of the movie.
肯尼:是的,那是我最爱看的一场戏,
Kenny: Yea right in the middle of my favorite seen where handy man bob
鲍伯把市长捆起来消失了.别,插上插头.
strips and vanishes the mayor, don't, plug it in.
本:好了.
Ben: Alright.
肯尼:太好了.为了将来不出乱子,我宣布本吸尘器不能用来吹树叶.
Kenny: Great, and for future reference the tornado vac is not used as a floatation device .
本:哦,不,他们来了.快点,帮我装进箱子里.
Ben: Oh no, it's my folks quick, help me get it back in the box .
麦琪:我真难以相信,你竟然买了四个备用轮胎.
Maggie: I can't believe you bought four factories of regular tires.
麦琪,轮胎总是要坏的,多买几个新的很正常.
Jason: Maggie a little shimmy is perfect natural of new tires .
麦琪:杰森,汽车的反光镜掉了.嗨,孩子们.
Maggie: Jason the rear view mirror fell of.Hi guys .
杰森:嘿,本,你把院子收拾的不错.
Jason: Hey Ben you did a great job in the yard .
本:谢谢,是肯尼拿耙子收拾的.
Ben: Thanks, Kenny grabbed a rake and pitched in .
杰森:怎么干的?我们只有一个耙子.
Jason: How?We only have one rake .
本:我们又做了一个.
Ben: We made another .
杰森:你做了个耙子?
Jason: You made a rake?
本:在技术上,是肯尼做的.他学过这个.
Ben: Technically Kenny made it, he was a boy scout .
肯尼:我做耙子得过奖章.
Kenny: Yea I got my mirth badge in rake making .
杰森:嘿,我想看看那个耙子.
Jason: Hey I gotta see this rake .
本:不,我看还是算了吧.
Ben: No, I mean you can't .
肯尼:不能泄露.
Kenny: Biodegradable.
本:是的,现在必须走,
Ben: Yea, and it's gone now,
肯尼一定要离开,我要确定他离开.
well Kenny has to leave and I have to make sure he does.
麦琪:做耙子的奖章?
Maggie: A rake making mirth badge?
你不觉得他们鬼鬼祟祟的吗?
Don't you find that just a little bit suspicious .
杰森:麦琪,别管本了.
Jason: Maggie we left Ben alone here, the house is still standing,
房子完好如初;上面没有警察的直升机盘旋.我们还是忙自己的吧.
there are no police helicopters circling above, I say we came out ahead.
卢克:迈克,我想跟你谈一会.
Luke: Mick I need to talk you got a second?
迈克:好的.
Mike: Yea sure.
卢克:哦,有点私事.
Luke: Well it's kinda private.
迈克:嘿,开萝尔,出去.
Mike: Hey Carol, get out .
开萝尔:决不.我在学习,所有的书都在这里.
Carol: No way, I'm studying and all my books are here.
迈克,我不想跟你咬文嚼字,
Mike I could give you a witty verbal retort you wouldn't understand,
你不会明白的,所以我还是用大白话说出来.
so let me put it in terms you're capable of comprehending .
迈克:好吧,兄弟,现在告诉我出什么事了.
Mike: Alright Luck my boy so tell me what's the problem
卢克:哦,学校里有个女孩叫苏伊士麦克斯韦. 我想可能喜欢上她了.
Luke: Well, there is this girl at school named Suez Maxwell and I think kinda sort of like her .
迈克:是吗,是可能吗?这是什么意思?
Mike: Yea, kinda sort of, what does that mean?
卢克:哦,她让我神魂颠倒的,我都不知道自己姓什么了.
Luke: Well she makes me sweat in places I didn't know I had glands .
迈克:哦,哦,这里有两个选择,约她出去,要不就忘了她.
Mike: Well then there is a choice you either go out with her or dehydrate .
卢克:我不能约她出去.
Luke: I can't ask her out .
迈克:为什么不能.什么问题?
Mike: Well why not, what's the problem?
卢克:呃,只是我从没约过人.
Luke: Me ah, I've never had a date before .
迈克:真的,你从来没…
Mike: Really you've never.
卢克:是的,我都15了,还从没约会过.
Luke: Yea that's right I'm 15 and I never had a date,
在大街上住的时候,你不用约人出去,你本来就在外边.
when you live on the streets you don't go out, you are out .
迈克:但那又怎样.本说过你在校园里是风云人物.
Mike: But so what, I mean, Ben says you're a pretty popular guy on campus.
卢克:没错,那是我一个人.
Luke: Sure, if I'm just hanging,
但如果我约苏伊士,我就得谈自己.
but if I go out with Suez I'll have to talk about myself.
"哦,苏伊士,
know Suez I think I'll missed the homecoming dance,
"我想你还不是很了解我的过去.我还是把自己的身世都告诉你吧".
I believe that was the night I was looking through the dumpster for shoes".
迈克:听着,女孩总归是女孩,
Mike: Now listen, girls are fragile creators anyway,
她们的感情脆弱.如果觉得她还没做好听你身世的准备,还是别告诉她了.
so if you think that she's not
ready to hear the whole story then don't tell it to her
卢克:那我该怎么回避呢?
Luke: Well how do I get around it?
迈克:把话题一直围绕她来展开.不像男生,
Mike: Keep bring the conversation back to her,
女孩总喜欢谈论自己.
unlike guys girls love to talk about themselves .
开萝尔:对不起,我插一下.
Carol: Excuse me, I beg to defer,
我就不是那样的,而且我从不这样.
I am nothing like that and further more I would never.
迈克:看到了吧,女孩就是这样.
Mike: See what I mean.
卢克:迈克,我真的喜欢苏伊士.
Luke: Mike I really like Suez .
迈克:哦,那就别楞着了,给她打电话.
Mike: Well then do yourself a favor go call her.
卢克:现在吗?
Luke: Now?
迈克:不!在她过15岁生日的时候.
Mike: No!when she celebrate her 15th birthday .
开萝尔:女孩感情脆弱.迈克,
Carol: Girls are fragile creators.
你根本不懂男女关系.
Mike you know absolutely nothing about relationships .
迈克:哦,我只知道我有凯特,而你什么也没有.
Mike: Oh well I know I have Kate and you have air .
开萝尔:听着,我敢打包票,
Carol: Listen socket head all I know is if he follows your advice he's
如果他听你的,一定会碰壁的.
going to get hurt .
卢克:迈克,她同意了.我们要去
Luke: Mike, she said yes, we're going to the hooky dooky frozen yogurt parley.
迈克:太好了,什么时候?
Mike: Alright, when?
卢克:我很快就回来.
Luke: I'll be right back .
克莉丝:爸爸,保龄球来了,小心点,很沉.
Chrissysie: Here is daddy blowing ball, be careful it's heavy.
麦琪:很好,亲爱的,
Maggie: Good honey, because the people who make this tornado vac claim
做吸尘器的人说可以把保龄球吸起来.
it can pick one up.
本:嘿,嘿,
Ben: Hey hey, so you're testing out that brand new,
你们正在检测这台崭新的,从来没用过的飓风牌吸尘器.
never used before tornado vac.
麦琪:噢,好了.大家注意你们的脚.宝贝,
Maggie: Uh huh, ok everybody watch your feet,
放好了,好,1,2,3.
sweetheart put it out here ok one, two, three.
本:哦,哦.
Ben: Oh oh.
麦琪:我早知道了.我又揭发了一件伪劣产品.我是消费者的守护神.
Maggie: I knew it, one more fraudulent claim exposed by Maggie Malone, consumer watch dog
本:哦,测试就这么完了.
Ben: Well that's a dumb test, when was the last time you said,
你上次还说过,我最好吸一下这块满是灰尘的地毯.
gee I better vacuum this carpet is full of blowing balls.
麦琪:本,也许在你看来是个玩笑,
Maggie: Ben this may seem like a joke to you but my column is very serious
但我的专栏是很严谨的.如果制造商向消费者撒谎,
business, when a manufacture lies to a consumer it is my job to tell the
我有责任公布真相,并揭发他们.好了,
consumer the truth no matter who gets hurt,
克莉丝,把烟灰倒到测试地毯上.
ok Chrissysie dump this ash on the test carpet.
本:就这样.
Ben: Great.
麦琪:我早知道这是件伪劣产品.
Maggie: I knew it this is a over price piece of junk and I'm going to
我要在专栏里写出来.
say so in my column .
本:那家公司会大发雷霆的.你想好了?
Ben: Couldn't tornado vac get mad and sue you?
麦琪:随便他们.我就是要说出真相.掌握真相,
Maggie: Let them, I'm just telling the truth and the truth makes me
我就是不可战胜的.实际上,我还控告他们赔偿我的一切损失呢.
invincible, in fact I dare them to sue me for every penny we've got .
本:快叫肯尼来.
Ben: Get Kenny now
苏伊士:今晚太糟糕了.我再也不让本推荐电影了.
Suez: Sorry about tonight, that's the last time I make Ben recommend a movie,
我从没见过这么糟糕的电影.好吧,说说你自己.
never look at a belt sander the same way again, so tell me about yourself.
卢克:我自己?
Luke: Myself?
苏伊士:是的,你以前在哪里?
Suez: Yea where were you before do we hi.
卢克:我在海上.
Luke: I was on this sea.
苏伊士:在海上?
Suez: On the sea.
卢克:啊,是的.我爸爸有一艘游船.
Luke: Aww yea, my dad owes a yacht .
苏伊士:哇,游船,多大的船?
Suez: Wow yacht, how big is it?
卢克:哦,就是一般大的那种游船.
Luke: Well you know the usual size for a yacht.
苏伊士:50英尺长吗?
Suez: Like 50ft .
卢克:对了.一艘非常漂亮的船,
Luke: Bingo and it's a real beauty but it's not as beautiful as your hair
但比起你的头发来就黯然失色了.你的头发真有光泽.
which is shiny as the napkin dispenser.
苏伊士:这真是太棒了,我们有很多共同语言.
Suez: You know this is so amazing we have a lot in common .
卢克:我们吗?
Luke: We do?
苏伊士:我爸爸参加过美洲杯帆船比赛.
Suez: My dad was on the Americans cup team,
我很小就开始航行了.
so I started sailing before I could walk .
卢克:我…我不知道这个.
Luke: I...I did not know that .
苏伊士:你参加过"女王"比赛吗?
Suez: Have you ever been Regina?
卢克:不,我参加过跑步比赛.
Luke: No.I was race party running.
苏伊士:那是赛艇比赛.
Suez: That's boat race.
卢克:一见你,我的心就砰砰跳.
Luke: I looking you make my heart race.
苏伊士:你不知道航海的事,是不是?
Suez: You don't know one thing about sailing do you?
卢克:我滑过船的.
Luke: With floats.
苏伊士:我早该想到了.你为什么骗我?
Suez: That's what I though, why are you lying to me?
卢克:因为我真的很喜欢…你听说过马尔格拉维阿国吗?
Luke: Because of who I really am,
have you ever heard of the country of Malgravia?
苏伊士:没有.
Suez: No.
卢克:如果我说你面前的就是那个国家流亡的太子呢?
Luke: Well what if I tell you you were looking at the crowned prince in exile.
苏伊士:我要说晚安,亲爱的太子.
Suez: I'd say goodnight sweet prince.
Chrissy: I hate Teddy Bowen, he threw my jacket in the mud
麦琪:看起来,他喜欢你了.
Maggie: Well I sounds to me that he likes you .
克莉丝:如果再他喜欢我,我就成那件倒霉的夹克了.
Chrissysy: If he likes me anymore I'm going to look like the swap thing.
麦琪:再帮帮,你帮我放脏东西,我来用吸尘器吸.
Maggie: Tell you what, let me put this in to soak and then you can
help me test the tornado vac
克莉丝:哦,不.
Chrissysy: Oh no!
麦琪:别这样,克莉丝,我换了一抬崭新的机器来测试.
Maggie: No chirsy, I return the first machine and got a brand new one to test.
克莉丝:我想帮你,可我要去睡午觉了.
Chrissy: I'd like to help but I think I'm due for a nap .
本:好,机器还在呢.
Ben: Good it's still here, Kenny yesterday this thing wouldn't pick up dust.
肯尼,昨天这东西坏了.你得把它修好.
you've got to give it some juice .
肯尼:没问题.好的,看这上面写着"不要打开".
Kenny: No problem, ok see that panel over there that says "do not open".
本:是的.是的.
Ben: Yea .
肯尼:打开.你看这根弹簧上写着"不要触摸".
Kenny: Open it, and you see that spring that says "do not touch".
本:啊.
Ben: Ahww.
肯尼:别碰,只要调一下,我就可以加大两倍马力.
Kenny: Don't touch it, one minor adjustment and I can double the power .
本:妈妈!
Ben: Mom!
麦琪:我还以为你们到外边打球了呢.
Maggie: I thought you guy were going to the mall?
本:我们是打算去的.可肯尼饿了,
Ben: We were going to but Kenny got hungry to we decided to have some
所以我们决定喝点牛奶,吃点饼干.我们一扫而光,
milk and cookies and clean up everything without a tract,
所以冰箱里没东西了.再见,肯尼.
which explains the empty sink, goodbye Kenny.
妈妈,肯尼刚才说有时候电压太低了,
Mom you know Kenny was telling me there was a lot of electrical stuff
会让电器出故障.
that can make an appliance act weird,
我想应该再测试一下那台飓风吸尘器.
I think we should give the tornado vac a second chance .
麦琪:本,我正有这个意思呢.
Maggie: I couldn't agree with you more Ben,
我现在就去测试去.
I'm going to go test it right now
本:我再也不动这个机器了.
Ben: "I must never use this power for evil".
迈克:卢克,你不该撒谎的.
Mike: Luke, look you shouldn't have lied.
卢克:是你告诉我不要把我的身世说给她听的.
Luke: You're the one who told me not to tell her the whole story .
迈克:我可没让你假冒什么马尔格拉维阿国的太子.
Mike: I didn't say anything about your birthright to the Malgravian thrown .
卢克:算了,都过去了.
Luke: That's it I'm done,
我不会再去约会了.
I'm going to give up this dating thing live by myself and learn to Weddle
就我一个人生活,潇洒大方.
and spit .
开萝尔:我就知道会是这个下场.我告诉过你,哈哈哈,对不起.
Carol: I knew it he's crushed, told you so ha ha ha.Sorry .
麦琪:杰森,杰森,杰森,快来啊,帮帮我.
Maggie: Jason!Jason, Jason, stop this thing , stop it .
杰森:坚持住,我比你有劲.
Jason: Hold on, I'm stronger than you.
麦琪:快把这东西搬出去.哦,我幸亏没把它弄到楼上去.要是把克莉丝伤着可坏了.
Maggie: Get this thing out of my house.Oh I had to divert it was heading for the straits I couldn't let it get Chrissyy
迈克:好家伙,这东西能吃人啊.
Mike: Man that thing tried to kill us .
本:得了吧,迈克,太夸张了.
Ben: Come on Mike don't exaggerate.
麦琪:不,迈克说的对.
Maggie: No mikes right yesterday I couldn't get it to suck up a dust bunny
昨天,它连灰尘都洗不起来;今天它又变成核能了.我要好好写篇文章.
today it has nuclear capabilities, well have I got to review the right,
本来只是工作上的事,现在是私事了.
this may have started out as business but now it's personal.
杰森:哦,啊,你可回来了.我修那堵墙的时候你跑哪儿去了?
Jason: Oh ho now you come home, where were you when I needed help fixing the living room wall.
迈克:哦,我一直在外边转悠,知道你干完了,我才回来,我不想因为说话影响你干活.
Mike: Oh well I was driving around the block till I knew you were finished, I didn't want your work to get in the way of my conversation.
杰森:什么话?
Jason: What conversation?
迈克:我只是想让你别修那堵墙了.爸爸,
Mike: The one I'm trying to have of you quit changing the subject,
我给卢克出了一个坏点子.
dad I think I gave Luke some bad advice.
杰森:坏点子?
Jason: You bad advice?
迈克:是的,他欺骗一个女孩.
Mike: Yea, he lied to girl .
杰森:是你教他…
Jason: And you told him to .
迈克:不,不,
Mike: No, no, he did it all on his own, the kids gifted,
是他自己这么做的.他有天赋.爸爸,
dad see look taught that is this certain girl knew about his pass days
卢克自己觉得要是那个女孩知道他到处流浪过,就会永远不跟他好了.
on the streets she would never want to go out with him.
杰森:那你的点子是?
Jason: And your advice was?
迈克:哦,我告诉他避开那段过去.
Mike: Well I told him he could skip that part if he wanted,
爸爸,我想这是在帮他的.
dad I thought I was sparing him .
杰森:迈克,卢克不需要回避那段经历.
Jason: Mike, Luke doesn't need sparing from his pass that's who he is,
这曾是他的生活,
just like running scams and taking advantage of people is part of who
就像喜欢刷滑头,作弄别人是你生活的一部分一样.
you are .
迈克:但爸爸,我以此为荣啊.
Mike: But dad I'm damn proud of that .
杰森:而卢克也完全可以以他为荣的.要想让别人接受自己,
Jason: And Luke could be proud of the young man that he is becoming,
他必须接受自己.
he just has to realize that he can accepted for himself.
麦琪:本,你在家干什么?我以为你到自助餐厅去吃午饭了.
Maggie: Ben, what are you doing home, I though you were going to eat lunch in the cafeteria?
本:能跟你谈谈吗,妈妈?
Ben: Can we talk mom?
麦琪:当然了,亲爱的,谈什么?
Maggie: Sure honey, what about?
本:我混蛋,我该死,我有救了.门铃响.
Ben: I'm scum, I'm slime, I'm saved, door bell.
道格拉斯:麦琪马龙,主妇专栏的作者.
Douglas: Maggie Marlon you stepford wife.
麦琪:道格拉斯司坦,你这家伙来了.本,这是我们报纸的编辑.道格,这是我儿子本.
Maggie: Douglas Stan you low rat blue garn, Ben this is my editor at the paper and Doug this is my son Ben.
道格拉斯:本,你就是那个跟洋娃娃睡觉的那个孩子.
Douglas: Ben, so you're the one that sleeps with the doll.
本:妈妈!
Ben: Mom!
麦琪:道格,那是10年前的事了.
Maggie: Doug that was ten years ago .
本:那不是洋娃娃,是会动的玩具.
Ben: It wasn't a doll, it was an action figure .
麦琪:怎么了,道格?看过我写的关于吸尘器的文章了,你喜欢吗?
Maggie: So what's up Doug I faxed you my vacuum piece, you liked it?
道格拉斯:我很喜欢.很尖锐,很深刻,可它被毙了.
Douglas: I loved it, it's biting it's insightful, it's death.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
道格拉斯:我准备拿下它.
Douglas: I'm going to have to kill it .
本:太好了.
Ben: Alright.
麦琪:道格拉斯司坦说真会开玩笑.
Maggie: Douglas Stan talk fast .
道格拉斯:飓风吸尘器公司是占姆公司的附属.
Douglas: Tornado vac is a subsidiary of gem core.
而包括我们在内的报业集团是幕后的大老板.
Which is wholly own and operated by misuesirou publications .
麦琪:什么意思?
Maggie: Which means?
道格拉斯:他们控制着我们,没办法的事.
Douglas: They own our paper and our pututies.
麦琪:为了这,你就不在乎我的第一条权利了.
Maggie: And for that you've going to infringe on my first amendment rights.
道格拉斯:你还有九条呢.我说麦琪,
Douglas: You got nine more, listen Maggie I'm sorry,
很抱歉,
in my honest opinion there isn't a newspaper in this town that would print
说实话,没有哪家报纸会刊登这篇文章的.
this,
我先走了,我还要去找另一个作者去呢,
look I got to run to replace this I got to sober up the guy that
他也是个惹麻烦的人.
writes dear aunt mable.
卢克:那么让我直说吧,
Luke: So let me get this straight,
你不但突然喜欢上菠萝酸奶酪了,
not only you get this sudden craving for pineapple yogurt,
还非得让我在一边看着你吃.
but you have to have somebody watch you eat it .
迈克:好吧,卢克,我来劝劝你.我想谈谈苏伊士,你上次错误地估计她了.
Mike: Alright Luke I'll level with you I want to talk about Suez, you got of on the wrong foot with her .
卢克:没开玩笑,如果能重新来过的话,
Luke: No kidding, if I could just go back and re-live those few minutes
我会收回那个谎言,再编一个更绝的.
wit her I would take it all back, make up a much better lie.
迈克:事实是,卢克,我敢打赌她还是不相信的.
Mike: The truth Luke, I'll bet she ready for it.
卢克:这有什么关系呢,我再也不打算见她了.
Luke: What does it matter, I'm never going to see her again.
苏伊士:我得到马尔格拉维阿国秘密警察送来的口信.
Suez: I got a note from the Malgravian secret police .
卢克:对不起,什么马尔格拉维阿国秘密警察?
Luke: Excuse me, the Malgravian secret police?
迈克:要想告诉他们真相,你得引起他们的注意.
Mike: Well before you can tell them the truth you got to get their attention.
好了,你说过想重新来过.快点来吧.
Alright now listen you said you wanted another change, well here you go .
卢克:啊,苏伊士,我想重新开始.
Luke: Ah, Suez I want to start over .
苏伊士:你为什么要编造那些不靠谱的故事呢?
Suez: Why did you make up all those wild stories.
卢克:哦,因为我喜欢你.
Luke: Well because I like you, I wanted you to like me to,
我想让你也喜欢我.但真相是我不是什么太子.
but the truth is I'm not the prince of anything,
我也没有什么游船,我更没有爬过珠穆朗玛峰.
I don't own a yacht and I didn't climb Mount Everest
苏伊士:你没说爬过珠穆朗玛峰啊.
Suez: You didn't say you climb Everest.
卢克:哦,还没来的及说呢.
Luke: Oh, you are before the chance.
苏伊士:我想喜欢你,可我还不了解你呢.
Suez: I'd like to like you but I don't even know you.
卢克:呃,几个月前,我还是个流浪儿.
Luke: Well up until a few months ago I was homeless.
苏伊士:哦,又来了.
Suez: Oh come on .
卢克:不,这是真的.我一直生活在大街上.
Luke: No I mean it, I was living on the streets.
如果你不喜欢,我很抱歉.但这事实就是这样的.
I'm sorry if that disgust you but that's the way it is .
苏伊士:你在大街上,那你睡在哪里呢?
Suez: Where did you sleep when you were on the streets?
卢克:走哪算哪.如果你想了解真相的话,那话可就长了.
Luke: Different places, if you want to know the truth it's a long story .
苏伊士:我有的是时间.
Suez: I've got time .
卢克:当我第一次来到这个城市…
Luke: When I first moved to the city....
露西:这位大胆的女士麦琪马龙要勇敢地检举一家丧尽天良,
Lucy: This courageous woman Maggie Marlon dares to speak out against the
坑害消费者的公司.
heartless cooperation Pedaling death door to door,
今天在19新闻频道露西施奈德专访节目中实况播出.
today on the Lucy Snyder segment channel 19 news live at 5.
摄像师:我们好了.
Camera man: And we're clear.
本:嘿,妈妈,你不担心如果,啊…这是干什么?
Ben: Hey mom you mind if ah...what's going on?
麦琪:本,那篇飓风吸尘器的报道也许让报纸受不了,
Maggie: Well Ben, my tornado vac story maybe to hot for the newspapers
可第19频道却很喜欢.我要在电视上揭发出来.
but it's not for channel 19, I'm telling my story live at 5.
肯尼:施奈德太太,消费者的知心朋友.
Kenny: Mrs.Snyder the consumer's best friend .
露西:是的,孩子,
Lucy: Yea kid, that's me.
就是我.好了.有谁愿意给我拿杯咖啡来?
Ok so who do you have to kiss around here to get some coffee?
麦琪:哦, 我在厨房里煮了一些.
Maggie: Well I've got some bruing in the kitchen.
露西:我只喝有咖啡因的.
Lucy: I don't drink de-cafe .
麦琪:哦,真遗憾.
Maggie: Oh pity.
本:肯尼,你必须得把这台吸尘器恢复正常.要不我们妈妈可丢大脸了.而且我们要赔偿损失的.
Ben: Kenny you got to get this machine back to normal before my mother humiliates herself and we're sued for every penny we've got .
肯尼:我正在修呢.
Kenny: I'm on it .
摄像师:嘿.
Camera man: Hey.
肯尼:我正拼装呢.
Kenny: I'm in the union .
麦琪:肯尼,你在干什么?
Maggie: Kenny what are you doing?
本:哦,妈妈.
Ben: Oh mom.
麦琪:本,我现在忙着呢.
Maggie: Look no Ben not now.
本:不,妈妈,你必须听我说.
Ben: Look no mom I think you have to hear this now .
麦琪:你做什么了?
Maggie: You did what?
肯尼:好了.
Kenny: Bingo.
摄像师:5,4,3,2…
Camera man : In 5, 4, 3, 2
露西:各位观众,
Lucy: Thank you Art and Coney,
今天我们故事的女主人公是一位勤劳,端庄的家庭主妇.
our story today is the heroine tell of a kind hardworking decent working
她将为大家讲述如何被一家公司欺骗并遭受重大损失的故事.
housewife who find herself a pone of a profit
麦琪,
mongered cooperation Maggie tell me Lucy Snyder about that tragic day
告诉露西那天你把飓风牌吸尘器带回家发生了什么悲惨的事情.
you brought that tornado vac into your home take your time .
这个,我不知道有什么好说的.
Maggie: Well I hardly know what to say .
露西:哦,不要紧张,我很关注.现在我们在直播呢,告诉我吧.
Lucy: Oh that's ok because I care , we're live dear talk to me now .
麦琪:这个,那台飓风吸尘器配备了3点5马力的发动机和手动开关.
Maggie:  Well, The tornado vac has a 3.5 horse power engine and finger tip controls
露西:你不是说它差点吸走你的孩子吗?
Lucy: Didn't you say it almost sucked up your baby,
你不想跟我们说点其他的吗?
I mean isn't there more you can share with us .
麦琪:哦,露西,
Maggie: Well Lucy as a customer report I wanted to see if the tornado
作为一个消费者顾问,我想看看这种吸尘器能不能像它所说的那样把保龄球吸起来.
vac could pick up a bowling ball as it claimed .
露西:好,我希望生产飓风牌吸尘器的那家公司正在收看我们的节目.
Lucy: Well I just hope the manufactures for tornado vac are watching .
麦琪:露西,哦,确实这样,它确实吸起了一个保龄球.它做到了.
Maggie: Lucy, oh it did it, it can pick up a bowling ball it did it .
露西:但是你说过它很危险啊?
Lucy: But you said it was dangerous?
麦琪:是对灰尘而言的,看看这个小垫子,
Maggie: Only to dirt, watch this little puppy suck up sandy mat,
上面简直什么都没有了.
it's like it was never there .
露西:但是,我想这种机器一定很昂贵了.
Lucy: But I bet they really doud you on the price.
麦琪:你在开玩笑吧?才买199块9毛5,到哪里去买这么便宜的.
Maggie: Are you kidding?It's only $199.95 you can't afford to be without one.
露西:哦,今天的节目就到这里.
Lucy: Well that's all the time we have for today .
麦琪:它还适合吸窗帘呢.
Maggie: And it has an attachment for drapes.
露西:节目就到这里.
Lucy: Back to you Art and Coney.
麦琪:你要不要试试啊?
Maggie: It that lint on your shoulders?
露西:离我远点.
Lucy: Stay away from me.
摄像师:时间到了.
Camera man: And we're clear.
麦琪:请你留步,先生.
Maggie: Hold it Mr.'s.
肯尼:我们干的真漂亮.呃,西沃太太.
Kenny: I did pretty good work huh Mrs.Sever
麦琪:再见,肯尼.
Maggie: Goodbye Kenny.
肯尼:回不回家应该是我说了算.现在可以回家了.
Kenny: For once I would like to be the one to decide when I go
home, now is good
本:妈妈,你不是说过,
Ben: Mom don't you think that the person who finally did the right thing
一个人要是最后做对了,并说出了真相,就该被原谅吗?
and told the truth shouldn't get punished .
麦琪:不,本,我觉得不管谁做错了,都要被惩罚.
Maggie: No Ben but I do think the punishment should fit the crime.
本:什么惩罚?00:22:29,800
Ben: What kind of punishment?